{ "questions": [
  {
    "question": "I am immensely proud of what I did for that turtle!",
    "incorrect": ["Pam", "Jim", "Michael"],
    "correct": "Kevin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Well, Happy Birthday Jesus. Sorry your party’s so lame.",
    "incorrect": ["Dwight", "Andy", "Meredith"],
    "correct": "Michael"
  },
  {
    "question": "I had feelings today for a coworker that I haven't had in years... In my defense he was grabbing my crotch fairly aggressively at the time.",
    "incorrect": ["Dwight", "Andy", "Gabe"],
    "correct": "Jim"
  },
  {
    "question": "Did I stutter?",
    "incorrect": ["Creed", "Oscar", "Kevin"],
    "correct": "Stanley"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm glad Michael's getting help. He has a lot of issues, and he's stupid.",
    "incorrect": ["Nelly", "Erin", "Andy"],
    "correct": "Phyllis"
  },
  {
    "question": "Two eyes. Two ears. A chin. A mouth. Ten fingers. Two nipples. A butt, two kneecaps, a penis. I've just described to you the Loch Ness monster. And the reward for his capture? All the riches in Scotland. So I have one question: Why are you here?",
    "incorrect": ["Andy", "Dwight", "Michael"],
    "correct": "Creed"
  },
  {
    "question": "Whenever I'm about to do something, I think, 'Would an idiot do that?' And if they would, I do not do that thing.",
    "incorrect": ["Jim", "Ryan", "Creed"],
    "correct": "Dwight"
  },
  {
    "question": "You can't let a girl feel good about herself. It will backfire on you. Every compliment has to be backhanded. 'Oh I like your dress, but I'd like it more if you had prettier hair.'",
    "incorrect": ["Darryl", "Toby", "Dwight"],
    "correct": "Andy"
  },

  {
    "question": "Everybody stay calm! Stay f*&#!#% calm!",
    "incorrect": ["Angela", "Meredith", "Andy"],
    "correct": "Michael"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have a lot of questions. Number one, how dare you?",
    "incorrect": ["Pam", "Erin", "Jim"],
    "correct": "Kelly"
  },
  {
    "question": "I feel God in this Chili’s tonight.",
    "incorrect": ["Roy", "Angela", "Kevin"],
    "correct": "Pam"
  },
  {
    "question": "I know that patience and loyalty are good, and virtuous traits. But sometimes I just think you need to grow a pair.",
    "incorrect": ["Oscar", "Darryl", "Jim"],
    "correct": "Angela"
  },
  {
    "question": "I. Declare. Bankruptcy!",
    "incorrect": ["Creed", "Kevin", "Meredith"],
    "correct": "Michael"
  },
  {
    "question": "I don't talk trash, I talk smack. They're totally different. Trash talk is hypothetical, like: Your mom is so fat she can eat the internet. But smack talk is happening like right now. Like: You're ugly and I know it for a fact 'cause I got the evidence right there.",
    "incorrect": ["Meredith", "Holly", "Jan"],
    "correct": "Kelly"
  },
  {
    "question": "In a gang world, we use something called fluffy fingers. That's when someone really gets in your face, you know you just, start ticklin' 'em. And he starts tickling you. And pretty soon you laughing and hugging. Before you know it, you've forgotten the whole thing. Y'all just go to church together, and get an ice cream cone.",
    "incorrect": ["Stanley", "Jim", "Michael"],
    "correct": "Darryl"
  },
  {
    "question": "Disposable cameras are fun, but it seems a little wasteful. You never get to see your pictures. If it's an important event that you want to remember, I recommend using a real camera.",
    "incorrect": ["Meredith", "Pam", "Michael"],
    "correct": "Erin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Shut up about the sun. SHUT UP ABOUT THE SUN!",
    "incorrect": ["Creed", "Kelly", "Erin"],
    "correct": "Gabe"
  },
  {
    "question": "If I had a gun with two bullets and I was in a room with Hitler, Bin Laden, and Toby, I would shoot Toby twice.",
    "incorrect": ["Dwight", "Jim", "Nelly"],
    "correct": "Michael"
  },
  {
    "question": "And I knew exactly what to do. But in a much more real sense, I had no idea what to do.",
    "incorrect": ["Kevin", "Andy", "Robert California"],
    "correct": "Michael"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bears, Beets, Battlestar Galactica.",
    "incorrect": ["Dwight", "Mose", "Andy"],
    "correct": "Jim"
  },
  {
    "question": "There’s a lot of beauty in ordinary things. Isn’t that kind of the point?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Jim",
      "Erin",
      "Karen"
    ],
    "correct": "Pam"
  }
]}
